<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="\\Ameras0036\Data\BIEM_PRODUCTION_AMERICA\053_NJT\Application\p-xml\XSL\053_NJT_ib.xslt" type="text/xsl"?>
<ib miid="BOM00773" doc-type="IP" maint-item-desc="Contract" doc-name="BOM00773_IP_0002" doc-title="MIM TS INTRO" lock-counter="20" search-index="" show-e-list="no" e-list-number="" giid-maint-item-desc="Contract" id-document="4143" id-document-version="305146" doc-version="8" pmt-version="77" sro-title="Introduction" user-defined-1="" user-defined-2="" user-defined-3="" oem-part-no="" device-name="">
	<integration-paragraph>
		<title id="ID200951922561818162">Troubleshooting</title>
		<topic>
			<para>Before fault isolation, perform a thorough visual equipment
inspection to determine if a malfunction is being caused by some
obvious defect such as a damaged component, defective wiring, etc.
Otherwise, fault isolation should follow a logical sequence designed
to isolate a malfunction to a single component.</para>
			<safety>
				<hazard level="notification" symbol="warning1">
					<hazard-desc>Before deciding that a system/subsystem is malfunctioning,
check that all related circuit breakers, switches, control devices,
and valves are set properly for normal operation.</hazard-desc>
				</hazard>
			</safety>
			<para>The fault isolation chart lists the symptoms most likely to
occur and suggests probable causes, identification and corrective
actions. The chart is made up of five columns. The first column,
FAULT CODE, lists the fault codes and diagnostic code if applicable
as found in the Interface Control Documents. The second column,
SYMPTOM, lists various failure symptoms. The third, PROBABLE CAUSE,
suggests at least one probable cause of a particular failure. The
fourth column, CHECK/INSPECT, suggests an action to identify each
probable cause, and the fifth column, CORRECTIVE ACTION, suggests
a corrective action. Both Inspect/Check and Corrective Action columns, when
applicable, refer to a task or document containing information that
could be of use to the reader. If a troubleshooting task is complex,
involves special tools, or requires illustration for understanding,
a TS task, to be found in the Maintenance Procedures, is referenced.</para>
		</topic>
	</integration-paragraph>
</ib>
